CHUKWUDI CHARLES OMEKE

Digital Marketer/Web Designer and Developer/IT Professional/UI/UX Designer

Tel: +2348167656064, +2349030057489

Email: charlesomeke45@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/charles-omeke-9337302b6/ Address: Port Harcourt Rivers State (Available to Relocate)

Professional Summary:

A solution-driven web developer very adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP, and JavaScript, Node JS. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, WordPress, UI/UX user experience, and speed.

Work experience:

Web Developer

Myteacher Services Limited

2022 - Till Date

Responsibilities:

Creating and maintaining website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS, JS, React Integrating data from various back-end services and databases

Gathering and refining specifications and requirements based on technical needs

Create and maintain software documentation

Responsible for maintaining, expanding, and scaling our site

Stay plugged into emerging technologies/industry trends and apply them to operations and activities.

UI/UX Designer/Web Designer (Web and App)

Ikefix Technology 2020 – 2021

Responsibilities

Developing UI/UX of web and app software

Selecting and organizing information for inclusion and designing the appearance, layout, and flow of the Website

Creating and optimizing content for the Website using a variety of graphics, database, animation, and other software

Research and evaluate a variety of interactive media software products

Led and co-ordinate multidisciplinary teams to develop Website graphics, content, capacity and interactivity

Education:

Web Development 2020 - 2021 Myteacher Institute

MSc. 2017 - 2020

University of Uyo Genetics

Core Skills:

Html, CSS, Javascript, React
PHP, MySQL
Node JS
WordPress
UI/UX Design
Mockup and designs
Software testing and deployment
Digital Marketing
Search Engine Optimization

Soft Skills:

Client focus Team work Organized Accurate

Hobbies:

Football Reading

Reference:

Available upon request